[
  {
    "name": "GNS",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What year is blah blah blah created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is GNS mandatory for a Management Science Student",
        "options": ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Not sure"],
        "answer": "Yes",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Given a person who earns blah blah amount per month and a spending rate of blah blah, what will remain out of his salary per year?",
        "options": [
          "2000 Naira",
          "13,250 Naira",
          "256.33 Naira",
          "42,672 Naira"
        ],
        "answer": "256.33 Naira",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "BUS",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What year is blah blah blah created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What year is foo foo foo created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is BUS mandatory for a Management Science Student",
        "options": ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Not sure"],
        "answer": "Yes",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Given a person who earns blah blah amount per month and a spending rate of blah blah, what will remain out of his salary per year?",
        "options": [
          "2000 Naira",
          "13,250 Naira",
          "256.33 Naira",
          "42,672 Naira"
        ],
        "answer": "256.33 Naira",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "ECN",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What year is blah blah blah created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What year is foo foo foo created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What year is bar bar bar created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is ECN mandatory for a Management Science Student",
        "options": ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Not sure"],
        "answer": "Yes",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Given a person who earns blah blah amount per month and a spending rate of blah blah, what will remain out of his salary per year?",
        "options": [
          "2000 Naira",
          "13,250 Naira",
          "256.33 Naira",
          "42,672 Naira"
        ],
        "answer": "256.33 Naira",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "ACC",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What year is blah blah blah created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": true
      },
      {
        "question": "What year is foo foo foo created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What year is bar bar bar created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "What year is baz baz baz created?",
        "options": ["1992", "1853", "2002", "1999"],
        "answer": "1853",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is ACC mandatory for a Management Science Student",
        "options": ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Not sure"],
        "answer": "Yes",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Given a person who earns blah blah amount per month and a spending rate of blah blah, what will remain out of his salary per year?",
        "options": [
          "2000 Naira",
          "13,250 Naira",
          "256.33 Naira",
          "42,672 Naira"
        ],
        "answer": "256.33 Naira",
        "userChoice": "",
        "correctStatus": false,
        "current": false
      }
    ]
  }
]
